[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This French car make was the first outside of the USA to produce automobiles for mass usage.", "correct_answer": "Citroen", "incorrect_answers": ["Renault", "None of these", "Peugeot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first trap seen in Saw II?", "correct_answer": "death mask", "incorrect_answers": ["furnace", "shotgun collar", "needle pit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call a group of flamingos?", "correct_answer": "Pat", "incorrect_answers": ["Family", "Pink", "Flock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movie does Bud Abbott \u201cprove to Lou Costello that 13 x 7 = 28?", "correct_answer": "In the Navy", "incorrect_answers": ["Splinters in the Navy", "Youre in the Navy", "Francis in the Navy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1971 one of the classics of the Film Noir genre was made in color - Chinatown.  The cast was stellar, as well as the director.  Can you name him?", "correct_answer": "Roman Polanski", "incorrect_answers": ["William Friedkin", "John Huston", "Billy Wilder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this company, founded by Fusajiro Yamauchi in 1889, roughly translates as leave luck to heaven.", "correct_answer": "Nintendo", "incorrect_answers": ["Toshiba", "Subaru", "Nokia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1995, a new Godzilla movie was released with the tagline Godzilla Dies.  Who was the Big Guys enemy in this film?", "correct_answer": "Destroyah", "incorrect_answers": ["King Ghidrah", "Megalon", "King Kong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The winner of a chess game is usually the player who made the penultimate mistake.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steve Rogers is the alter ego of this character.", "correct_answer": "Cpt America", "incorrect_answers": ["Cpt Marvel", "Spiderman", "Superman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The song Moonriver is featured in the musical Grease, starring John Travolta.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fish from the title of the 1988 comedy movie starring John Cleese?", "correct_answer": "Wanda", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilma", "Susan", "Betty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What musical instrument did Richard Gere study when he was a student?", "correct_answer": "Trumpet", "incorrect_answers": ["Organ", "Violin", "Guitar"]}]